<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>StatSVN News</title>
    <link>http://www.statsvn.org</link>
    <description>StatSVN News</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2007 StatSVN Sourceforge Development Group &amp; ObjectLab</copyright>
	
	<item>
		<title>This RSS is discontinued, please switch to ObjectLab Open Source news for news about StatSVN.</title>
		<description>This RSS feed is discontinued, please switch to <a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/ObjectLabOpenSourceNews">ObjectLab Open Source News</a> for news about StatSVN.
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN publishes stats for JDK7, JBoss, ServiceMix, JRuby, Commons-Lang, TestNG, Maven 2, Maven 2 plugins and Continuum.</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released statistics for the following project:</p>
<ol>
	<li><strong>JDK7</strong> The java JDK version 7! Checkout the very latest changes!</li>
	<li><strong>JBoss AS</strong> No less! Do not try this at home, the first batch of statistics required 102,000 calls to the server... now it is fast!</li>
	<li><strong>JRuby</strong> is an 100% pure-Java implementation of the Ruby programming language!</li>
	<li><strong>ServiceMix</strong> The Apache ServiceMix project is an ESB and component suite based on the Java Business Interface (JBI) standard - JSR 208</li>
	<li><strong>Commons-Lang</strong> The Apache Commons Lang.</li>
	<li><strong>TestNG</strong> the new testing framework!</li>
	<li><strong>Maven 2</strong> The Apache Maven 2!</li>
	<li><strong>Maven 2 Plugins</strong> The Apache Maven 2 Plugins!</li>
	<li><strong>Continuum</strong> The Apache Continuum project!</li>
</ol>
<p>The line of code cache is also published.</p>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
<p>Also, we took the liberty to add a few ads, please support us...</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN publishes stats for QALab, ObjectLabKit, PZFileReader, XStream, Ant libs, etc.</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released statistics for the following project:</p>
<ol>
    <li>QALab: A great tool for keeping track of QA statistics over time.</li>
    <li>PZFileReader: Parsing of delimited strings or fixed-length strings.</li>
    <li>ObjectLab Kit: Date Calculators for Business and Finance.</li>
    <li>JTreeMap: Heat Map library.</li>
    <li>AntLibs DotNet.</li>
    <li>AntLibs Subversion.</li>
    <li>AntLibs Ant Unit.</li>
    <li>XStream: XStream is a simple library to serialize objects to XML and back again.</li>
</ol>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN publishes stats for Apache QPid.</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released statistics for the Apache QPid project, multi-language implementation of AMQP, Advanced Messaged Queuing Protocol.</p>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN publishes stats for Apache Synapse.</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released statistics for the Apache Synapse project.</p>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN adds Demos for Subversion, Mule, Ant and Spring RC.</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released a few more 'demos' for Ant, Subversion, Spring Rich Client and Mule.</p>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>New StatSVN Demos:Apache Felix, Apache Log4J, Ruby, Groovy, Grails, etc</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released a few 'demos' against some well known open source projects, the list will grow but currently includes Groovy, Grails, Ruby, Log4J, Apache Felix, Spring Rich Client, Hibernate3 and Joda-Time.</p>
<p>See <a href="http://www.statsvn.org/demo">http://www.statsvn.org/demo</a></p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>StatSVN Demos on some Open Source projects?</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>StatSVN has released a few 'demos' against some well known open source projects, the list will grow but currently includes Spring Rich Client, Hibernate3 and Joda-Time. See http://www.statsvn.org/demo.</p>
<p>Feel free to suggest some projects, they must be well-known!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Interested in contributing to StatSVN?</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>Want to help? We're considering replacing our command line invocations with calls to <a href="http://www.svnkit.com">SVNKit</a> (formerly JavaSVN). Want to write the prototype implementation and see how well it performs? Let us know!</p>
	]]></description>
	</item>
	
	
	
    <item>
      <title>StatSVN version 0.3.0 released</title>
      <link>http://www.statsvn.org</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<p>The StatSVN Team and ObjectLab are proud to announce v0.3.0 of StatSVN</p>

<p>If you want to know what happened in your Subversion repository,
this is the tool for you!</p>

<p>StatSVN retrieves information from a Subversion repository and generates
various tables and charts describing the project evolution, e.g.
the lines of code over time, contribution of each developer, the
evolution of modules, directories, files, the time and days when most
checkins happen, etc. It also shows the commit logs and integrates 
out of the box with ViewVc, BugZilla, Chora and others.</p>

<p>The new version of StatSVN generates a static suite of HTML or XDoc
documents containing tables and chart images.</p>

<h2>Version 0.3.0 includes, amongst others:</h2>

<ul>
<li>New Line of Code and 'Churn' page that shows the evolution of LOC and
  the number of lines touched. This gives a sense of the kind of activity
  (new lines or re-working existing lines)</li>
<li>New and dynamic repo based on JTreeMap that at a glance, shows the
  last 30 days of changes in your repo. It is possible to drill down and
  is very visual (based on an applet that requires jdk 5 jre).</li>
<li>Fetching the line diff is now multi-threaded (25) by default if a call
  to the server takes more than 2 seconds. Both threshold and threads
  are configurable.</li>
<li>Added 'experimental' support for SymbolicLinks (tags).</li>
<li>Based on StatCVS 0.3 (plus one fix for ViewVC with Ant).</li>
<li>A number of fixes and improvements.</li>
</ul>

<p>The new XDoc support enables a basic level of integration of the stats
in a maven build.  This is demonstrated on the following page:
<a href="http://www.statsvn.org/statsvn">http://www.statsvn.org/statsvn</a>.</p>

<p>StatSVN is available now for download at <a href="http://www.statsvn.org">http://www.statsvn.org</a>.</p>

<p>StatSVN is open source software, released under the terms of the LGPL,
based on StatCVS, it uses JFreeChart and JTreeMap to generate charts.</p>

<hr/>
 
<p>ObjectLab is not new to the open-source community having used numerous OS 
projects, participated in a few and sponsoring:</p>
<ul><li>ObjectLab Kit (<a href="http://objectlabkit.sourceforge.net">http://objectlabkit.sourceforge.net</a>), a date calculation 
  toolkit for business and finance;</li>
<li>JTreeMap (<a href="http://jtreemap.sourceforge.net">http://jtreemap.sourceforge.net</a>) the only open source heatmap 
  library for Java </li>
<li>QALab (<a href="http://qalab.sourceforge.net">http://qalab.sourceforge.net</a>) QA Statistics for your build (now 
  also integrated in JBuilder 2007).</li>
</ul>  

<p>We would like to thank our friends and colleagues for their help, reviews 
and suggestions.</p>

<p>Feel free to pass on to people who may be interested.</p>

<p>Enjoy!!</p>

<p>The StatSVN Team and ObjectLab.</p>
      ]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>